goldmap.blogspot.com 2009-12-31

# Doing Business: Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

If you require any more information or have any questions about our  
privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at  

At [goldmap.blogspot.com](http://goldmap.blogspot.com/), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme  
importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of  
personal information is received and collected by [goldmap.blogspot.com](http://goldmap.blogspot.com/)  
and how it is used.

Log Files

Like many other Web sites, [goldmap.blogspot.com](http://goldmap.blogspot.com/) makes use of log files.  
The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP )  
addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ),  
date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze  
trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and  
gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such  
information are not linked to any information that is personally  
identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons

[goldmap.blogspot.com](http://goldmap.blogspot.com/) does use cookies to store information about  
visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages  
the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors  
browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their  
browser.

DoubleClick DART Cookie

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on [goldmap.blogspot.com](http://goldmap.blogspot.com/).

.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users  
based on their visit to [goldmap.blogspot.com](http://goldmap.blogspot.com/) and other sites on the  
Internet.

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the  
Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL -  

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....  
Google Adsense  
Bidvertiser  
Amazon  
Adgitize

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to  
the advertisements and links that appear on [goldmap.blogspot.com](http://goldmap.blogspot.com/) send  
directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address  
when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or  
Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to  
measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to  
personalize the advertising content that you see.

[goldmap.blogspot.com](http://goldmap.blogspot.com/) has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these  
third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices  
as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.  
[goldmap.blogspot.com](http://goldmap.blogspot.com/)'s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot  
control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your  
individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie  
management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers'  
respective websites.
